<Document>
	# Preamble
	NanoTrasen mandates that members of [color=red][bold]Security[/bold][/color] and [color=yellow][bold]Command[/bold][/color] personnel operate under an abbreviated Space Law. Below is a written list of clauses laid out as a series of bullet points that may readily and rapidly be referenced by number.

	The exact meaning of terms may be referenced in the <!-- TODO make this a textlink later -->Definitions page. Terms with a listed definition will be marked in [color=#7af][bold]blue and bold[/bold][/color]

	Failure to follow Space Law on duty constitutes as a [bold]3-04 - Neglect of Law[/bold] criminal charge, and is most likely to be enforced by adherent members of [color=red]Security[/color], if, of course, possible or reasonable in the moment.

	<!-- TODO format/style the bulletpoints to not lucky ugly as fuck with the markdown and be easy on the eyes to read. some fuckery with tables? -->
	<!-- TODO nuke all the comments because fsr they invariably produce a linebreak. i hate xaml i hate guidebooks -->
	<!-- TODO identify all the terms that need defining and slap them in the Definitions page -->
	<!-- TODO add a section 0. defining who is and isn't protected by cslaw? old slaw says foreign invaders aren't protected but it needs to be more than vibes -->
	<!-- TODO related ^ section 0. could define that contradictory bulletpoints could be resolved by points above taking precedence? like silicon laws -->

	# Space Law

	## 1. Treatment of Prisoners

	- 1.1. Prisoners must be granted adequate medical care in confinement.
	- - 1.1.1. Prisoners must have their corporeal wounds treated before or during confinement.
	- - 1.1.2. Prisoners must have access to medical equipment necessary for survival, ergo N2 internals gear granted to Vox.
	- - 1.1.3. Prisoners must be granted disability aids while in confinement, ergo canes granted to mobility impaired persons.

	- 1.2. Prisoners must be granted adequate sustenance (food & water).
	- - 1.2.1. Sustenance granted to inmates must be consumable and digestible by the inmate, ergo allicin or theobromine free food granted to allergic species, cloth or fiber granted to Moth People.

	- 1.3. Prisoners must not be [color=#7af][bold]restrained[/bold][/color] while in confinement, with the following exceptions.
	- - 1.3.1. Prisoners may be temporarily restrained when being relocated between confinement areas.
	- - 1.3.2. Prisoners may be temporarily restrained to mitigate risk to life or limb of other persons or restrained prisoner.
	- - 1.3.3. Prisoners may be temporarily restrained if the confinement area is unable to contain the prisoner, due to structural damage or otherwise.

	- 1.4. Prisoners must be granted access to working headsets while in confinement.
	- - 1.4.1. Headsets confirmed to contain contraband radio keys may <!-- TODO may? -->be confiscated and returned with the keys removed, or replaced immediately.
	- - 1.4.2. Abuse of communications may be acted upon by temporary confiscation of headset until end of confinement. <!-- TODO may? what constitutes abuse? -->

	- 1.5. Prisoners must be held in a safe environment with no undue risk to life or limb.
	- - 1.5.1. If Genpop is damaged or becomes uninhabitable, confinement must be established elsewhere and repairs be made immediately. <!-- this is more a clarification than a clause but that's probably fine? -->
	- - 1.5.2. <!-- anyting else? there's probably more you can say about this -->

	- 1.6. Prisoners must be granted adequate clothing while in confinement.
	- 1.6.1. Clothing rejected by prisoners for practical or preferential reasons must be provided with alternatives <!-- you cannot forcefem or forcemasc the prisoners -->
	- 1.6.2  Uniforms and shoes must be available to prisoners at all times. Outer clothing or head garments may be provided on request. <!-- TODO may? -->
	- 1.6.3. Clothing items may not be forced onto prisoners by other persons if the prisoner rejects them. <!-- fucking timmy will throw off his jumpsuit and icl it's better to just let him -->

	- 1.7. Non-contraband items must be returned to prisoners after confinement is concluded <!-- TODO might be better suited for section 4. or 5. i guess? -->
	- 1.7.1 Non-contraband items used in the crime leading to arrest and sentence may be confiscated indefinitely. <!-- bartender can't keep dbarell they shot the clown to death with & tider can't keep their soap and insuls -->
	- 1.7.2. Essential items such as PDAs or job critical equipment must be returned or replaced after confiscation.

	<!-- TODO i wanted to include a "prisoners may not be injured or disabled while in confinement" (read: can't use Mk 58 or disabler fnr) but idk how to word it not awkwardly -->

	## 2. Apprehension and Escalation
	<!-- half life two bawawawaun bawaunn -->
	<!-- TODO should there be a clause dictating prisoners must know their charges when arrested? -->
	- 2.1. 

	## 3. Sentencing and Action

	## 4. Search and Seizure

	## 5. Posession and Provision

	## 6. Implantation and Implant Removal

	## 7.
	<!-- TODO: uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh -->

</Document>
