<Document>
	# Space Law
	NanoTrasen mandates that members of [color=red][bold]Security[/bold][/color] and [color=yellow][bold]Command[/bold][/color] personnel operate under an abbreviated Space Law. Below is a written list of clauses laid out as a series of bullet points that may readily and rapidly be referenced by number.

	The exact meaning of terms may be referenced in the <!-- TODO make this a textlink later -->Definitions page. Terms with a listed definition will be marked in [color=#7af][bold]blue and bold[/bold][/color]

	Failure to follow Space Law on duty constitutes as a [bold]3-04 - Neglect of Law[/bold] criminal charge, and is most likely to be enforced by adherent members of [color=red]Security[/color], if, of course, possible or reasonable in the moment.


	## 1. Treatment of Prisoners

	- 1.1. Prisoners must be granted adequate medical care in confinement.
	- - 1.1.1. Prisoners must have access to medical equipment necessary for survival, ergo N2 internals gear granted to Vox.

	- 1.2. Prisoners must be granted adequate sustenance (food & water) on demand.
	- - 1.2.1. Sustenance granted to inmates must be consumable and digestible by the inmate, ergo allicin or theobromine free food granted to allergic species, cloth or fiber granted to Moth People.
	- - 1.2.2. Demands for sustenance must be met in a timely manner when possible, ergo when unburdened by more pressing matters or situations.

	- 1.3. Prisoners must not be [color=#7af][bold]restrained[/bold][/color] while in confinement.

	- 1.4. Prisoners must be granted access to basic equipment while in confinement. With the following exceptions.
	- - 1.4.1. PDAs, headsets, and disability aids must be granted to prisoners at all times - unless possession of them poses an immediate risk to life and limb, or may aid in criminal activity - <!-- TODO: clarify as aiding escape or murking someone--> in which case they may be confiscated and replacements provided posthaste.<!-- TODO:posthaste???????-->
	- - 1.4.2. Basic articles of clothing such as shoes and jumpsuits must be readily available within confinement, and may not be coercively removed by other persons.

	- 1.5. Prisoners may not be injured or disabled in confinement, unless it is required to mitigate immediate harm to life and limb to other persons, or to carry out an authorized execution.

	- 1.6. Prisoners must be held in a safe environment with no undue risk to life and limb.
	- - 1.6.1. If Genpop is damaged or becomes uninhabitable, confinement must be established elsewhere and repairs be made immediately.

	## 2. Apprehension and Escalation
	<!-- half life two bawawawaun bawaunn -->

	## 3. Sentencing and Action

	## 4. Search and Seizure

	## 5. Posession and Provision

	## 6. Implantation and Implant Removal

	## 7.
	<!-- TODO: uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh -->

</Document>
