<Document>
  # Core Rule 5 - Do not use out of game methods to communicate with other players

  Engaging in voice chat while you are in game with another player participating in said voice chat is very hard to moderate. It is nearly impossible to prove that you are not in a vc with the intention to metagame. These behaviours may result in administrative action or being flagged by an admin. Communicating over other platforms should only be done at your risk.

  Even if information is not being shared or abused, it may still be considered a violation of this rule. Due to the difficulty of determining if information is being shared, it will almost always be presumed that people who message another player they are in a round with, or who are in a voice call with another player during a round are sharing round information.

  ## Teaching new players
  Teaching new players through "metacomms" is acceptable in our server culture. This does not mean abusing this to cheat, but players and admins alike here all understand that getting introduced to SS14 is challenging. Ideally this would be communicated to an admin prior or made known to the general server so that people are aware of what is happening. It is still expected of players to not reveal crucial round information regardless.

  ## Streaming
  Public livestreams are not exempt from this rule, but have different liability. Using information from a public live stream of the game (stream sniping) is a violation of this rule. Watching a public live stream of the game while connected to the same server is a violation of this rule. Allowing people watching a public live stream to share information about the current round, for example through the stream's chat, is a violation of this rule. Using that information is also a violation of this rule. Sharing information about the current round with a streamer is a violation of this rule if that information was obtained from any source but the stream. The stream's moderators are expected to enforce this on the streaming platform in addition to any in-game enforcement done by game admins.

  Public livestreaming by itself is not a violation of the rule as long as the stream is sufficiently moderated. Streamers are encouraged, but not required, to use a stream delay.

  ## Exceptions

  - Public information like round manifests or announcements (such as the emergency shuttle being called) that can be seen by players withing the lobby, are not to be considered metacomming.
  - News broadcasts are not considered metacomms, as they are publically accessed by all players and will be published to our Discord server.
</Document>
